[Boyd] Previously on From...
[screams]
[people scream]
[Marielle] Nicky,
stay with me, okay?
Sheriff Boyd, I can't
take back what I did.
- You killed someone!
- I...
And you left two people
to die in that ambulance!
- I know!
- One of whom
you handcuffed to
a fucking wall!
I am sorry.
[Henry] Miranda
started seeing things.
She said it was like
she'd been chosen to
free the children.
I guess you've been
chosen now, too.
Miranda... she's
the only one who had
a connection to this place
long before she arrived.
[Tabitha] What is this?
Did you see three red stones?
How did you...
When I was a little girl,
I would have the same
nightmare over and over again.
It wasn't just Miranda.
I saw this place, too.
[chittering]
[grunting]
[Randall] If you'd seen
the things I've seen...
What are you talking about?
What do you think I'm
talking about, Boyd?
When me, Julie and Marielle,
wherever we were...
Everybody here just talks about
how afraid they are of dying.
Well, I don't think
that's the worst thing
that can happen to you here.
I feel like something
is watching me.
Is that her? She looks scary.
[gasps]
Help me, Elgin. I
can save all of you.
Donna, I was told
I can't have kids.
What's happening right now
is medically impossible.
You're gonna have a baby
that you were told
you could never have!
With all you've seen, you can't
wrap your head around a miracle?
[beeping]
I don't see anything.
[Fatima] That's impossible.
You barely looked!
Just keep looking!
You're not pregnant.
And how long have these
cravings been going on for?
Um, about a week maybe?
Guys, what is happening to me?
Um, well, I mean, if
we were anywhere else,
I'd say your body's
exhibiting signs
of a psychosomatic pregnancy.
And what is that?
It's a fairly rare condition
where your body
believes it's pregnant.
It shows all the early
signs and symptoms of...
"Hysterical pregnancy."
Isn't that what they
used to call it?
Hey, no one here thinks
you're being hysterical.
It wasn't so long ago
that Boyd had worms under his
skin that no one else could see.
We're not ruling
anything out here.
And, I mean, you very well
could have been pregnant...
I am pregnant. It's still
there! I can feel it.
Here. Just take a sip of this.
- I don't fucking want that!
- [glass shatters]
[Kristi] Okay...
Sorry. I'm sorry.
[Kristi] It's been a long day.
Your body's been
under a lot of stress.
[exhaling deeply]
How about you stay the night?
Ellis can stay, too, and...
- I wanna go home.
- [Kristi] Fatima...
I just wanna go back to my room.
It's raining outside, okay?
I don't want you walking...
You're worried about
the fucking rain?!
Okay.
- Hey.
- Fatima!
Hey, you go. You should go.
Fatima!
- [Fatima] I wanna go home!
- [door opens]
I'm gonna go stay the
night at Colony House.
At least I can
get an IV started.
- Yeah.
- [door closes]
You should've told me about all
of that before the ultrasound.
- It wasn't my place.
- Really, Boyd?
Now you wanna stand on ceremony?
That was information I could
have used before the exam.
I can't help, if
I'm in the dark!
You wanna yell at me?
Fine, but once you're done,
can we maybe figure out
what we're gonna do now?
I don't know what
we're gonna do.
I don't know what's
wrong. Either way, she...
she has something growing
inside of her that we can't see,
or this place has finally
gotten to her head
and made her believe
she's pregnant.
Okay. Then, how do we
figure out which one it is?
I don't know, Boyd.
Then how do we help her?
I have no fucking
clue how to help her.
Okay. Then, do your fucking
job and figure it out!
[heavy rainfall]
["Que Sera, Sera (Whatever
Will Be, Will Be)" plays]
♪ When I was just a little boy ♪
♪ I asked my father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be handsome?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ Here's what he said to me ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
♪ Now I have
children of my own ♪
♪ They ask their father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be pretty?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ I tell them tenderly ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
I'm not scared.
You need to talk.
You... talk! I
know you can talk!
You need to talk to me!
[knock on door]
[murmuring]
[Henry] Uh, Victor?
It's... it's me.
Can I come in?
Victor, you can't
keep doing this.
You were up all night. You've
been in here all morning.
I could hear you yelling at
that thing from downstairs.
Son...
Now, this isn't healthy.
He needs... he needs to talk,
and he needs to tell me...
- Hey...
- tell me what he said.
Yeah, but it's... it's a doll.
Right? I mean you...
You don't understand.
You weren't there.
Look, Victor, maybe
just take a break...
- I can't do this here!
- No. Why don't...
- I can't do this.
- Victor!
Victor!
Hey. Whatcha workin' on?
Oh, it's just a little...
I'm making this for Fatima.
[gasps] Oh!
You know, I thought, she's
been pretty down lately,
and I thought maybe
this might cheer her up.
Well, that's just adorable.
I'm sure she'll love it.
I hope so.
Mm.
[camera shutter clicks, whirs]
[ominous music playing]
♪♪♪
You're lucky that new
ambulance came in.
All Kristi had before was
saline in glass bottles.
Yeah, so lucky. [sighs]
Hey.
I know last night was a lot.
- Do you?
- I do.
I also know what it's like to
feel violated by this place.
What happened to me
and Julie and Randall,
there are still times
I can feel those bugs
crawling around inside me.
And what do you do?
I remind myself it isn't
real, that it's just fear,
and fear can only
break me if I let it.
This is different.
You don't know that.
Yes, I do!
[sighs]
Maybe you could just try
eating regular food again,
just small bites.
I'm not eating garbage
because I'm afraid
or... or broken.
It's... it's happening because
it's... it's making me.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I was just finishing up.
[exhales heavily]
I'll see you tomorrow, okay?
[door closes]
She just cares about you.
Why isn't anybody
listening to me?
It's happening inside of me.
I'm the one experiencing this!
Why is my fucking point of view
the only one everybody
assumes is wrong?
Nobody's assuming that
you're wrong. Okay?
We're... We're just
trying to see this
from every possible
angle we can.
And you? Do you think
this is all in my head?
[scoffs]
Look, ever since that night
at the Sheriff's Station,
when the bus pulled into town,
you... you broke down in my arms.
Do you remember that? You said
you couldn't take it anymore...
This has nothing
to do with that!
Okay, so then tell me
what am I supposed to do?
Believe me!
Look, look, okay.
Just... Ow!
Ugh!
Look!
Just...
I have been measuring every
single day since I found out.
- You just need to stop.
- And my stomach...
And my stomach is
getting bigger!
- Baby, it's not...
- Look! Look at it! Look!
If this is in my
head, how do you...
how do you explain
my body changing?
- I don't know.
- Ellis...
whatever is inside me,
it's getting stronger.
The... the fucking cravings,
they're getting stronger.
Please.
- I'm angry all the time.
- It's okay.
If there's nothing there,
if the baby isn't real,
that means that it's me.
[crying]
I told her it was a miracle.
Yeah, we all, uh...
[clears throat]
We all got a little excited.
[sighs]
You're sure there's no way
Kristi missed anything?
Donna, there was nothing there.
Nothing that showed up
on that machine anyway.
So, the way Kristi sees it,
either there's something there,
like the worms that
were under my skin,
or this place
finally got to her.
Like Abby.
Yeah, like Abby.
Look, if you're thinking about
things you could have
done different...
- No, it's not that.
- Well, it should be.
Look, if it's some
kind of fucked-up
worms-under-the-skin type thing,
then that's a bridge
we're gonna have to cross.
But if it's psychological,
if she's anywhere near
the place Abby was in,
then we need to figure out
a way to bring her back.
Okay, well, let's just...
make sure this stays between us.
And then what?
I'm gonna have a talk
with Kristi later.
Hopefully, she'll have
had time to, uh...
To what?
I don't know. Look.
Look, I... I'm
just telling you
'cause you and I promised not
to keep secrets from each other,
and she's living
under your roof.
Yeah, yeah.
About that... While
we're figuring it out,
I don't think it's a good idea
that they stay at Colony House.
What?!
Look, I am gonna
be there for them,
for you, every step of the way.
But the truth is, there
are two possibilities here,
and each one poses a
different kind of threat
to the people of that house.
I have to think about
everyone here, Boyd,
no matter how much I
wanna help you guys.
Okay, I, uh... I
guess I can, uh...
make some space at
the Sheriff's Station.
- I gotta...
- Oh, Boyd, come on.
No, we're good! We're good!
I'm not saying it
has to be today.
I'm just saying it's
something we have to consider.
I get it! You're
not wrong! Okay?
You and me, we're
okay. Just... I just...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know. I know.
This one's all right.
Let me help you. If
we get going soon,
we should be able to make
pretty good time back to town.
Whatever was banging
around last night
sure as hell didn't sound like
those things back in town.
Whatever it was,
I'll be glad when this
place is in the rearview.
[Ethan] Is this what
was in your dream?
Yeah.
What the hell?
Tabitha?
Dad!
Hey. What happened?
- Nothing.
- Where's Julie?
Oh, she's... she's
fine. Everything's okay.
What the hell's going on?
[Jade] Listen, it's okay.
All right? It was my idea.
She needed to come out here.
Why?
Mom saw this place
when she was little,
just like Victor's mom.
What?
Jim! You coming or staying?
Uh, you guys go on ahead.
We'll... we'll catch up.
Suit yourself.
Come on. Let's go look around.
Let's go.
Hey.
You moving in?
Yeah, I asked Kristi if
I could spend the night.
- Why?
- [door closes]
My whole family's
at the settlement.
So?
So, it's fucking creepy
in that house by myself.
What's wrong with you?
- Nothing.
- So, we got high on the bus
together and now you're gonna
be all weird towards me?
I'm not being weird.
Where you going?
For a walk.
- Want some company?
- Nope.
'Kay, let me put my bag inside.
[grunts]
[ominous music plays]
♪♪♪
[exhaling]
[hinges squeak]
♪♪♪
[doors creak]
[knock on door]
[knocking resumes]
♪♪♪
[wood scraping, creaking]
[sighs]
Oh, hey. Uh...
Sorry, we're not, uh...
We don't really serve
food here anymore,
if that's what
you're hoping for.
Why is there a diner here?
Sorry?
And why is there a
Sheriff's Station
that looks like a post office?
Or a goddamn, uh,
travel agency sign?
I mean, what kind of
psycho built this place?
You want... you want me to
go over them one at a time
or you want me...
I wanna know why no one's
asking those questions.
[sighs] We did.
And?
Want some tea?
This place is creepy.
Yeah, it certainly is.
Who do you think lived out here?
I don't know.
What do you think
happened to them?
Maybe, uh... maybe
they got out.
You know, maybe they went home.
Just careful where
you're stepping, 'kay?
Why?
Bear traps.
Seriously.
I'm just saying, given
everything that's happened,
there might be a part of you
that wants so badly for
all of this to make sense.
Do you think I'm making this up?
Of course not.
You had a dream, a
terrifying dream,
when you were little.
This wasn't just a
random nightmare, Jim.
This was a dream I had, over
and over again, for months,
and every night, I
would wake up screaming.
So, when I tell you
that the totems here
are the same ones that
I saw in my dream...
what do you want me to
do? Give up? Stop trying?
I don't know.
[exhales]
Look, Tabby, this place,
I thought I had it
all figured out,
and I almost got Donna killed.
Sara? She heard voices,
and she tried to
murder our child.
- But that's different.
- Why?
Those things happened once
we got here, but my dream...
I was a kid!
I know you're scared.
I'm scared, too.
But these things
are happening to me.
I-I can't pretend they're not.
One way or another,
I need to know.
Okay.
So, my mom is convinced
that these creepy children she
keeps seeing need her help.
And my dad's all,
like, freaked out
'cause the last time he
went down a rabbit hole
about this place, he
almost got everyone killed,
including this
one complete idiot
who tied Donna to a tree
in the middle of the woods.
Yeah.
Are you listening?
Yeah, of course. Yeah.
Your mom and the
kids, rabbit stuff...
[chuckles] What are
you looking for?
What? Uh... chaga.
It's a mushroom.
Grows in cold weather.
Marielle and Kristi are on
some holistic foraging trip.
So, where were you
going, on the bus?
Detroit. Like everyone else.
Why?
To buy a car, so I didn't have
to ride the fucking bus anymore.
- That true?
- No.
I never even got my
learner's permit.
What?
Yeah, you're supposed to
get it when you're 15.
Everything kinda stopped
after Thomas died.
That's your brother?
Yeah. My dad was supposed
to take me to the DMV,
but we never got
back from our trip.
Uh...
All right, uh... Come with me.
Where are you going?
Can you just come on?
You have to understand,
uh, things are...
things are a little different
when you first get here.
I mean, you show up, and
you think to yourself,
"I'm gonna figure this out.
All these other people,
they may have given up,
they may have accepted it.
But me? I'm gonna
figure this out.
I'm gonna be the one
who gets to go home."
- And what's wrong with that?
- Nothing.
Completely normal. But, uh...
given some time, it'll pass.
Pass. [stammers]
Sorry. No, that's the thing.
The whole idea of just
throwing up your hands
and saying, "Oh, well, I tried"?
That's not how I'm built.
Right. You're not the type to
just accept the world as it is.
What?
I've had this
conversation before,
and I've been on the
other side of it.
The thing you come
to realize is that...
every... [sighs]
question you're asking
has been asked before.
Every theory that you have,
someone else has had before
you, and at some point,
you either adapt or
you lose your mind.
So, that's what you
did? You adapted?
Well, me, I didn't
really have a choice.
When I first got here,
I was so busy taking care
of my dad that I was just...
Your... dad?
He passed away.
And your mom... she...
she used to run the diner?
Mm-hmm.
You lost both your parents here?
Yeah. [scoffs]
I'm really sorry.
Thanks.
You're... welcome.
Um, what about,
uh, what about you?
You have any... you
have a family back home?
Uh, no, not...
Um... not really.
Right.
Um, the good news is that
we have the talismans,
and they keep us safe at night.
So, you know... I mean,
that wasn't always the case.
What the hell did
people do before?
They just...
tried to hide as
best they could.
Jesus.
Yeah. I wasn't here then.
There aren't many
people left who were.
Where did they come
from? The talismans.
Uh...
Boyd. He, uh...
found 'em out in the
forest one night.
So, that's why he acts like
the God king of the world.
It's, uh, not like that.
You sure?
I mean, no offense, the
guy's kind of a dick.
You, uh, didn't exactly
meet him under the
best of circumstances.
He took my gun.
Can you blame him?
You know, I'm gonna have to
carry the weight of that...
of what I did, for
the rest of my life.
I know that. But
for him to f...
Hey, you know they have
tons of fresh clothes
up at Colony House.
You'd be a lot more
comfortable, if you...
You know, I don't want your
fucking fresh clothes, okay?!
No offense, really! I
don't want your tea.
And I don't want your
adapt-or-die philosophy.
I don't plan on getting
comfortable here, okay?
I'm gonna figure the...
["O-o-h Child" by Five
Starships playing]
Yeah, they uh... They
do that sometimes.
♪♪♪
Is that something else
you get comfortable with?
♪ Ooh, ooh, child ♪
♪ Things are gonna
get easier... ♪
Look, thanks for the tea.
Uh, you didn't even...
Excuse me.
♪ Ooh, ooh, child ♪
♪ Things are
gonna Get easier ♪
She's taking it well.
♪ Ooh, ooh, child ♪
Yeah. Uh, you need something?
♪ Someday... ♪
Yeah. [sighs]
Yeah, actually.
Um, I was hoping I
could talk to you
about reopening the diner.
♪ Yeah, we'll walk in the
rays of a beautiful sun ♪
[metal screeching]
[ominous music playing]
♪♪♪
[gasping]
Is this really where it happens?
[pounding on door]
Hi.
Can I go in your basement?
Why?
Because I need him
to tell me a secret.
'Kay, isn't this,
like, for emergencies?
This is an emergency.
Just get in. Come on.
Let's go.
All right.
Ahh. Okay.
- All right. Bingo.
- [keys jangle]
What you wanna do...
You gotta pay attention.
[engine sputters, turns over]
You turn it on, you press
in the clutch, okay?
Make sure this has been shifted,
then you're gonna ease
off the clutch, right?
[engine revving]
Voilà.
[sighing deeply]
Henry.
You need something?
I... could use a drink.
You know what?
So could I.
Let's go.
[clattering]
Who's in there?
Hello?
What the fuck are you doing?
You took my gun.
I want it back.
You... Get out.
Fine. Give me my gun,
and I'll be on my way.
Hey, hey, hey! I don't
have time for this today!
I don't give a shit
what you have time for!
You shot someone!
A girl is dead
because you panicked!
Yeah, I panicked because I
was being chased in the dark
by things that should only
exist in a fucking nightmare!
Well, they exist here,
and they're going to
continue to exist.
So, until you prove that
you can handle that,
there is not a chance in hell
you're getting anywhere
close to a loaded gun!
[chuckles]
I don't have to
prove shit to you.
You see this?
I'm a cop.
A real one,
not just walking around in
some hand-me-down blazer,
playing make-believe.
Right. And when did you
get out of the academy?
Two days? Three?
That's none of your business.
That's where you are wrong.
Everything about
you is my business.
This place is my
business. You know why?
Why?
Because I'm the one who
makes sure people stay safe.
I am the one who
keeps people alive!
Wow. Well, from what I hear,
you've been doing a pretty
shit job of that lately.
Get the fuck out!
Fucking place...
Hey...
Give me... my gun.
You want your gun?
Correct.
You want your gun.
[sighs]
[gun clicking]
[clicking]
There's your gun.
You get your bullets when
I think you deserve them.
[scoffs]
Hey!
The next time you come in
here without my permission,
you and me are gonna
have a problem.
Whatever you say, "Sheriff."
This fucking kid...
I'd ask you what
you were drinking,
but the menu here's
kinda limited.
Everything going all
right with Victor?
Things are going, um...
No, I don't think they are.
[coughs]
You okay?
Yeah. [breathes deeply]
[exhales sharply]
I stood there today in his room,
and I... [sighs]
I had a thought I'll never
forgive myself for. [sniffs]
I wished I had never come here,
I wished Tabitha
had never found me,
because it was easier when
I thought he was dead.
It was only for a second.
What kind of father thinks
that about his child?
Here.
Yeah. [sniffles]
- Mm.
- [glass clatters]
Are these the same
ones from your dream?
It's not just the stones;
it's everything. It's...
It's how it feels.
I still remember the
fear when I was running.
I started over there
and came to hide
behind the rocks.
Which one?
This one.
And then what?
Whatever was making
everyone scream
was on the other
side of this rock.
And I would look up and...
What?
I would wake up
every single time.
Okay, let's say you
actually did see this
place before we came here.
Yeah, like...
like Miranda did.
[Jim] How does that help?
Maybe Aristotle got it wrong.
You know, free will and
determinism, it's...
Miranda said she was chosen.
Right?
If seeing this place, you
know, visions, dreams...
if that's the proof...
and you saw this
place as a child?
You never really had
a chance, did you?
[Jim] What...
What do you mean?
If fate exists, if
you were destined
to come to this place
since you were a child...
then, one way or another,
you were always gonna come
to that tree in the road.
How's Fatima doing?
Oh. [clears throat]
She's, uh... She's good.
You know, we're just taking
things one step at a time.
You don't have to pretend.
She told me about the rotten
food, about the cravings.
I realize you don't
know me very well.
But if you need
anything, I'm here.
We did an ultrasound last night.
There was a machine
on the ambulance.
And? Is the baby okay?
There is no baby.
When Kristi examined
her, she looked.
There was nothing there.
So, it's either there's
something inside of her
that isn't human, that
a machine can't see,
or this place has
just broken her mind.
[kettle whistling]
I just... I can't
lose her. I just...
[kettle whistle slows and stops]
You haven't lost her.
She's still here, Ellis.
A good friend once said to me,
"Enjoy every moment,
and don't grieve the living
before they're gone."
And that's what I told my family
when I got my diagnosis.
Are you afraid?
Of dying?
Sure, at first, I was.
And then I got angry.
And one day, I realized
just how small life is,
how it all goes by so fast.
You start to wonder how
it could be anything
but the beginning of
some grand adventure,
or maybe it's the middle,
but I don't think it's the end.
Not anymore. Once
I realized that,
things didn't seem so scary.
None of us get to stay forever.
I don't need
forever. I just...
Whatever I can do,
whatever you need...
well, it may not be
much, but I'm here.
Mm?
I'm sorry, but why? I
mean, you barely know us.
I'm old, and I have cancer.
I like a good love
story. That work for you?
Yeah. Yeah, that...
that works fine.
Hm. Come on.
[coughing]
[gasping in pain]
[breathing heavily]
[whimpering]
[screaming in pain]
[screaming] Help!
Help!
[gasping]
Help. Help.
Help!
[whimpering]
Fatima?
[gasping]
Hey, babe, what's
wrong? What happened?
[breathing rapidly]
What's... What's
happening to me?
[breathing heavily]
Oh, God...
- I can't...
- [Tillie] Ellis?
It's fine.
[whimpering and sobbing]
Hey. It's okay.
Whoo! Goddamn,
this feels good.
So, am I gonna get
a turn or what?
All right.
Okay, okay. A
promise is a promise.
- [chittering]
- Fuck.
What's going on?
Nothing, nothing.
Uh, the, um... [clears throat]
Son of a bitch.
[chittering]
Yeah, fuck you!
What are you doing?
- You don't see 'em?
- See what?
It's the fucking...
it's the fucking bugs!
- The ones that...
- No.
- [chittering]
- No, no, no, no, no.
[chittering]
- [Julie] Randall!
- Fuck you, man!
Randall, stop!
- [tires screeching]
- [chittering]
Randall!
Get the fuck off me!
Randall, hey! What are you...
Get the fuck off!
What the fuck?
What just happened?
Just go the fuck home.
- Hey!
- Get off me!
- Randall! Come back!
- Go home, Julie!
[Kristi] Hey! Put
those back! Ellis!
[Ellis] Look! She's in pain,
okay? I need to do something!
- Ellis! Hey!
- Thank you for all your help...
Hey, hey, what the
hell is going on?
Your son decided to come in here
and root the medicine cabinet!
Yeah, that's because
that ambulance has plenty
of emergency medications!
This isn't fucking aspirin
we're talking about!
Things that can make
her stay calm, okay?
These are powerful
anti-psychotics!
You have no idea what kind
of damage that could cause!
Okay, so what then? What? What?
We're just gonna do nothing?
Okay, you're not the one
that's sitting there,
- watching her go to pieces!
- No, I'm the doctor, okay?
And it is my job to use my
brain and not my emotions
- when making decisions.
- All right.
Ellis, those pills in your hands
could make things a lot worse.
Give them back to me.
[Boyd] Give her the bottle.
Give her the
fucking bottle, man.
Ellis! Ellis! Hey!
What?!
Look, I know you're scared, man.
What am I supposed to do?!
Huh?!
Tell me, what the fuck
am I supposed to do?!
- I don't know.
- Okay, I-I saw it!
I saw what happened
with your fucking worms!
And I saw what happened to...
I saw what happened
to Mom when she...
Which fucking nightmare am
I supposed to be afraid of?
Which?
You know, she's
fucking falling apart,
right in front of me, and
I don't know what to do.
I can't do anything to help her.
Dad, I don't know
how to help her.
- It's all right.
- Please...
- [Boyd] Yeah.
- Don't let this happen, Dad.
Okay.
I...
It's just, uh...
Randall?
[breathing heavily]
Randall?!
[ominous music plays]
[Randall] Julie!
What the hell is that?
I don't know.
What happened to you back there?
Why did you just
run off like that?
I'll tell you on the way back.
- Come on.
- Wait.
Do you feel that?
Julie, we should go.
No. No, I wanna check it out.
Hey, hey, stop.
Stop.
You do. You feel it.
I don't feel shit.
Okay?
It's gonna be dark soon.
We gotta get that van
back to Colony House.
All right, let's just...
let's just go.
Please?
♪♪♪
[sighs]
[exhales deeply]
[exhales]
[gasps loudly]
[gasping in pain]
- [whimpers, screams]
- [Tillie] Fatima?
- Ooh, Fatima!
- [groaning loudly]
- Listen to me.
- [gasps in pain]
- You're not alone.
- Please go.
- I'm gonna help you!
- Get off me.
Everything is gonna be okay.
- Just go!
- It's gonna be okay.
- I said go!
- [gasps]
I'm so... Tillie, Tillie...
No, no. No, no, Tillie,
Tillie, Tillie! I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean it! I...
Help!
Help! Help!
You have to run.
[breathing rapidly]
Ellis, what have I done?
What have I done?!
♪♪♪